Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records UA042
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Surveys and reports, 1900 -- 2007; 1965 -- 1999; UA042.001; 56.4 Linear Feet; 139 Digital Object(s)
  - Alumni Association 172 (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Tufts Name Policy (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Fact Book Use (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - International Students by Country (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Average SAT Scores of Entering Class (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Full-Time Student Enrollment (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Graduating Seniors by Major (first majors)/Graduating Seniors by Major (first, second, third) (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Paid Personnel/Paid Personnel by EEOC Category/Paid Personnel by Home Address (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00028; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Characteristics of Entering Classes - Undergrad ASE (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00029; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Characteristics of Entering Classes - Grad and Prof (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Top Countries Represented (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00031; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - International Students - Summer ESL (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Summer Session Enrollments (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00033; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - All Person Holding Paid Faculty Appt. / Tenure and Tenure Eligible Faculty / International Faculty and Scholars by Country (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00034; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Library Collections / Interlibrary Loans / Library Statistics / Library Expenditures (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Endowment Funds / Add/Deduct from Endowment / Private Contributions and Grants (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00036; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Alumni/ae who Received Degrees (1,2,3,4) / Multiple Degree Holders / Living Alumni/ae by Country / Living Alumni/ae Total Breakdown / Living Alumni/ae by State (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00037; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Student to Faculty Ratio (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00038; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Undergraduate Tuition and Fees / Prof. Schools Tuition Rates (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00039; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Average Full-Time Faculty Salary (Fact Book), 2004 -- 2005; UA042.001.040.00040; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey Trends [1 of 2], 1989 -- 2004; UA042.001.040.00041; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey Trends [2 of 2], 1989 -- 2004; UA042.001.040.00042; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey Noms and Misc. [1 of 3], 1992 -- 2001; UA042.001.040.00043; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey Noms and Misc. [2 of 3], 1992 -- 2001; UA042.001.040.00044; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey Noms and Misc. [3 of 3], 1992 -- 2001; UA042.001.040.00045; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey (1) [1 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.040.00046; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey (1) [2 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.040.00047; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey (1) [3 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.040.00048; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey (2) [1 of 4], 2004; UA042.001.040.00049; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey (2) [2 of 4], 2004; UA042.001.040.00050; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey (2) [3 of 4], 2004; UA042.001.040.00051; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey (2) [4 of 4], 2004; UA042.001.040.00052; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey [1 of 2], 2005; UA042.001.040.00053; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey [2 of 2], 2005; UA042.001.040.00054; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey [1 of 2], 2006; UA042.001.040.00055; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Senior Survey [2 of 2], 2006; UA042.001.040.00056; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Tufts University New Student Questionnaire, 2000; UA042.001.040.00057; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - Tufts University Non-Enrolling Student Questionnaire, 2000; UA042.001.040.00058; Office of Institutional Research (Box 40)
  - AAUP, 1994 -- 2001; UA042.001.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - AAUP Annual Survey of Faculty Compensation, 1995; UA042.001.041.00002 (Box 41)
  - Accepted App, 2000; UA042.001.041.00003 (Box 41)
  - Accepted App - Preliminary Reports [1 of 2], 2000; UA042.001.041.00004 (Box 41)
  - Accepted App - Preliminary Reports [2 of 2], 2000; UA042.001.041.00005 (Box 41)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Preliminary Report, 1990; UA042.001.041.00006 (Box 41)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Preliminary Report, 1991; UA042.001.041.00007 (Box 41)
  - Accepted Applicant Study Preliminary Report, 1994; UA042.001.041.00008 (Box 41)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey [binder], 1990; UA042.001.041.00009 (Box 41)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Instruments [binder], 1983 -- 1993; UA042.001.041.00010 (Box 41)
  - Accepted Applicant Survey Report on Reasons for not Coming to Tufts, 1993; UA042.001.041.00011 (Box 41)
  - Accepted Applicant Surveys [binder], 1983 -- 1988; UA042.001.041.00012 (Box 41)
  - Accepted Students Survey Draft, 2001; UA042.001.041.00013 (Box 41)
  - Admission - New Student Survey Preview, 2001; UA042.001.041.00014 (Box 41)
  - Admissions College Choice - Accepted Applicants 1989, UA042.001.041.00015 (Box 41)
  - Advising Data, 1991 -- 1998; UA042.001.041.00016 (Box 41)
  - All Students (merge file), 1975 -- 2000; UA042.001.041.00017 (Box 41)
  - Alumni Opinion Survey, 1975; UA042.001.041.00018 (Box 41)
  - Alumni Survey Frequencies, 1989 -- 1994; UA042.001.041.00019 (Box 41)
  - Alumni Survey Classes, 1989 -- 1994; UA042.001.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Alumni Survey Draft, 2001; UA042.001.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - Alumni/AE Survey, 1989 -- 2001; UA042.001.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Project on Visibility and Loyalty, 2001; UA042.001.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - Asian Student Study, 1984 -- 1985; UA042.001.042.00005 (Box 42)
  - Boston Housing Study, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.042.00006 (Box 42)
  - Boston Housing Study, 1991; UA042.001.042.00007 (Box 42)
  - CGS/GRE Survey - Total Grad Enrollment Data Sheet, 1999; UA042.001.042.00008 (Box 42)
  - Class of 1952 Survey Instrument, 2001; UA042.001.042.00009 (Box 42)
  - Class of 1963 35th Reunion Survey, 1998; UA042.001.042.00010 (Box 42)
  - Class of 1968 35th Reunion Survey, 2003; UA042.001.042.00011 (Box 42)
  - Coding/Data Entry Manual Accepted Applicant Survey [binder], 1989; UA042.001.042.00012 (Box 42)
  - Comparison of Tufts University with Peer HEDS/COFHE Institutions Senior Survey Responses, 1998; UA042.001.042.00013 (Box 42)
  - Comparitive Study of How Universities Service Boards, 1991; UA042.001.042.00014 (Box 42)
  - Comparitive Study of How Universities Service Boards, 1993; UA042.001.042.00015 (Box 42)
  - Dental School, 1997; UA042.001.042.00016 (Box 42)
  - Dental School Comparitive Report, 1986 -- 1987; UA042.001.042.00017 (Box 42)
  - Dining, 2002; UA042.001.042.00018 (Box 42)
  - Eight Year Summary of Post-Graduate Plans for the Classes of 1988-1995, UA042.001.042.00019 (Box 42)
  - Endowed Chairs, 2001; UA042.001.042.00020 (Box 42)
  - Engineering Alumni, 2000 -- 2001; UA042.001.042.00021 (Box 42)
  - Enrollment and Faculty Line Graph, 1991 -- 1996; UA042.001.042.00022 (Box 42)
  - Enrollment Study, 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.042.00023 (Box 42)
  - Enrollment Study Charts, 1991 -- 1999; UA042.001.042.00024 (Box 42)
  - Enrollment Study Charts, 1991 -- 1996; UA042.001.042.00025 (Box 42)
  - Enrollment Study Class Size and Tenure Status, 1991 -- 1997; UA042.001.042.00026 (Box 42)
  - Enrollment Study Graphs - All Departments [1 of 3], 1991 -- 2002; UA042.001.042.00027 (Box 42)
  - Enrollment Study Graphs - All Departments [2 of 3], 1991 -- 2002; UA042.001.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Enrollment Study Graphs - All Departments [3 of 3], 1991 -- 2002; UA042.001.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - Enrollment Study Raw, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - Enrollment Study Raw Data, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - Enrollment Study Report, 1991 -- 2003; UA042.001.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - Enrollment Study Summaries, 1991 -- 1998; UA042.001.043.00006 (Box 43)
  - EPIIC Evaluation, 2003; UA042.001.043.00007 (Box 43)
  - Ethnicity Breakdown Compared With Other Schools and Within Tufts, 1999; UA042.001.043.00008 (Box 43)
  - Evaluation of Web-Based News Services, 1998; UA042.001.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - First Monitoring Report of "Recommendations from the Report of the Ad-Hoc Committee on Institutional Policy", 1997; UA042.001.043.00010 (Box 43)
  - Financial Aid Stat in Fact Book, 2002; UA042.001.043.00011 (Box 43)
  - Fletcher School Course Evaluation Questionnaire - Fall, 1999; UA042.001.043.00012 (Box 43)
  - Fletcher School Course Evaluation Questionnaire - Spring, 1999; UA042.001.043.00013 (Box 43)
  - Fletcher School Course Evaluation Questionnaire - Summer, 1999; UA042.001.043.00014 (Box 43)
  - Fletcher School Course Evaluation Questionnaire - Spring, 2000; UA042.001.043.00015 (Box 43)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Accepted Applicant Survey, 1992; UA042.001.043.00016 (Box 43)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Rejected Applicant Survey, 1990; UA042.001.043.00017 (Box 43)
  - Freshmen Financial Aid Packages Class of 2000, 1997; UA042.001.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - Fund-Raising Proceeds: A Comparison of Twenty Three Private Universities, 1976 -- 1984; UA042.001.044.00002 (Box 44)
  - Grade Distributions, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.044.00004 (Box 44)
  - Greenworks, 1992; UA042.001.044.00005 (Box 44)
  - GSAS, 2000; UA042.001.044.00006 (Box 44)
  - GSAS Exit - School Psych Trends, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.044.00007 (Box 44)
  - GSAS Exiting Student Survey, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.044.00008 (Box 44)
  - GSAS Graduate Student Survey, 1997; UA042.001.044.00009 (Box 44)
  - GSAS HEDS Web Survey, 1999; UA042.001.044.00010 (Box 44)
  - Guidance Counselor Survey Draft, 1980 -- 2000; UA042.001.044.00011 (Box 44)
  - Health Center Boston Campus Housing Study, 1986; UA042.001.044.00012 (Box 44)
  - Health Education Survey, 1989; UA042.001.044.00013 (Box 44)
  - Health Education Survey, 1990; UA042.001.044.00014 (Box 44)
  - Health Education Survey, 1991; UA042.001.044.00015 (Box 44)
  - Health Service Appointment/Walk-In Survey, 1993; UA042.001.044.00016 (Box 44)
  - Health Survey, 1994; UA042.001.044.00017 (Box 44)
  - HEDS, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.044.00018 (Box 44)
  - HEDS Alumni Survey Files, 1998 -- 2000; UA042.001.044.00019 (Box 44)
  - HEFA Questionnaire, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.044.00020 (Box 44)
  - Hispanic American Survey, 1995; UA042.001.044.00021 (Box 44)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute UBSEP Grant Request, 1989 -- 1995; UA042.001.044.00022 (Box 44)
  - Hughes Project, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.044.00023 (Box 44)
  - Information Technology Task Force, 1996; UA042.001.044.00024 (Box 44)
  - Integrated Marketing Survey, 2001; UA042.001.044.00025 (Box 44)
  - Intellectual Property, 1998; UA042.001.044.00026 (Box 44)
  - Intellectual Life, 1995; UA042.001.044.00027 (Box 44)
  - International Center, 1993; UA042.001.044.00028 (Box 44)
  - International Orientation, 1998; UA042.001.044.00029 (Box 44)
  - Internship Programs, 1994; UA042.001.044.00030 (Box 44)
  - Inventory, 1997; UA042.001.044.00031 (Box 44)
  - Inventory - Space, 1999; UA042.001.044.00032 (Box 44)
  - Jobs by Primary Major - Senior Survey, 2000; UA042.001.044.00033 (Box 44)
  - IPEDS - Faculty Salaries, 1988 -- 1989; UA042.001.044.00034 (Box 44)
  - IPEDS - Faculty Salaries, 1989 -- 1995; UA042.001.044.00035 (Box 44)
  - IPEDS - Faculty Salaries, 1989; UA042.001.044.00036 (Box 44)
  - Library Report, 1999; UA042.001.044.00037 (Box 44)
  - Med School Comparative Report, 1989; UA042.001.044.00038 (Box 44)
  - Med School Stat, 1993; UA042.001.044.00039 (Box 44)
  - Mellon Foundation College and Beyond Study, 1996; UA042.001.044.00040 (Box 44)
  - NACUBO Benchmarking Project, 1991; UA042.001.044.00041 (Box 44)
  - NACUBO Endowment Study Questionnaire for Fiscal Year, 1989; UA042.001.044.00042 (Box 44)
  - NACUBO Endowment Study Questionnaire for Fiscal Year, 1993; UA042.001.044.00043 (Box 44)
  - NACUBO Endowment Study Questionnaire for Fiscal Year, 1994; UA042.001.044.00044 (Box 44)
  - NACUBO Endowment Study Questionnaire for Fiscal Year, 1995; UA042.001.044.00045 (Box 44)
  - NACUBO Endowment Study Questionnaire for Fiscal Year, 1996; UA042.001.044.00046 (Box 44)
  - NACUBO Endowment Study Questionnaire for Fiscal Year, 1997; UA042.001.044.00047 (Box 44)
  - NACUBO Endowment Study Questionnaire for Fiscal Year, 1988; UA042.001.045.00001 (Box 45)
    The label on the folder says 1998 but the files within the folder are dated 1988
  - NACUBO Endowment Study Questionnaire for Fiscal Year, 1998; UA042.001.045.00002 (Box 45)
  - New Student Survey, 1994; UA042.001.045.00003 (Box 45)
  - Non-Matriculating Comments [binder], 1986; UA042.001.045.00004 (Box 45)
  - NSF Survey of Research and Development Expenditures at Universities and Colleges, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.045.00005 (Box 45)
  - NSF Survey of Research and Development Expenditures at Universities and Colleges, 1996; UA042.001.045.00006 (Box 45)
  - Operations Training Survey, 1997; UA042.001.045.00007 (Box 45)
  - Orientation, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.045.00008 (Box 45)
  - Positions on Tufts Tested, 2001; UA042.001.045.00009 (Box 45)
  - Pre Major Advising Survey - Liberal Arts and Engineering, 1998; UA042.001.045.00010 (Box 45)
  - Public Safety/Boston, 1980 -- 2000; UA042.001.045.00011 (Box 45)
  - Recommendations from the Report of the Task force on race - Responses, 1999; UA042.001.045.00012 (Box 45)
  - Renovation Plans/Process, 1987; UA042.001.045.00013 (Box 45)
  - Report on Faculty Appointments, 1996; UA042.001.045.00014 (Box 45)
  - Retention Statistics - Minorities, 1990 -- 1991; UA042.001.045.00015 (Box 45)
  - Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Services Admissions Inquiry Survey [binder], 1990; UA042.001.045.00016 (Box 45)
  - Senior Survey Preview - Class of 1997, UA042.001.045.00017 (Box 45)
  - Senior Survey - Report of Importance/Satisfaction of Campus Services and Aspects, 1999; UA042.001.045.00018 (Box 45)
  - Sophomore Career Planning I, 1997; UA042.001.045.00019 (Box 45)
  - Sophomore Career Planning II, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.045.00020 (Box 45)
  - Sophomore Experience and First-Year Engineering Advising Survey, 2001; UA042.001.045.00021 (Box 45)
  - Sophomore Survey - Comments and Preview, 2001; UA042.001.045.00022 (Box 45)
  - Student Services Center, 2001; UA042.001.045.00023 (Box 45)
  - A Study of Trends in Minority Applications, Acceptances, and Enrollment at Tufts University, 1972 -- 1984; UA042.001.045.00024 (Box 45)
  - Survey of Chemistry Departments, 1997; UA042.001.045.00025 (Box 45)
  - Talloires Re-assessment/Evaluation Questions, 2001; UA042.001.045.00026 (Box 45)
  - Task Force on Race Interim Report, 1997; UA042.001.045.00027 (Box 45)
  - Task Force on the Undergraduate Experience Faculty Survey, 2002; UA042.001.045.00028 (Box 45)
  - Teaching Load Data, 1998 -- 2000; UA042.001.045.00029 (Box 45)
  - Tisch Library Survey - Faculty, 1998; UA042.001.045.00030 (Box 45)
  - Tisch Library Survey - Spring, 1997; UA042.001.045.00031 (Box 45)
  - The Tufts University Alcohol Study, 2001; UA042.001.045.00032 (Box 45)
  - Tufts University Class of 1952 50th Reunion Questionnaire, 2002; UA042.001.045.00033 (Box 45)
  - Tufts University Joint Peer Leader Training Program Orientation, 1999; UA042.001.045.00034 (Box 45)
  - Tufts University Residential Student Survey, 2001 -- 2002; UA042.001.045.00035 (Box 45)
  - Tufts University Study of Applicants to Medical School, 1997; UA042.001.045.00036 (Box 45)
  - TUSDM Alumni/Alumnae Survey - Class of 1992 and 1995, 1997; UA042.001.045.00037 (Box 45)
  - TUSDM Alumni Class of 93 and 96 Comparison, 1993 -- 1996; UA042.001.046.00001 (Box 46)
  - TUSDM Faculty Survey, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.046.00002 (Box 46)
  - TUSDM Strategic Goals, 1999; UA042.001.046.00003 (Box 46)
  - TUSDM Trends, 1991 -- 1996; UA042.001.046.00004 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM 4th Year Students, 1994; UA042.001.046.00005 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM 4th Year Students, 1995; UA042.001.046.00006 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM 4th Year Students Combined, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.046.00007 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Alumni, 1983 -- 1992; UA042.001.046.00008 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Alumni and Recent Graduates: Likeliness to Pursue DVM and Enroll at TUSVM Again, 1995; UA042.001.046.00009 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Correlation Study, 1983 -- 1990; UA042.001.046.00010 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Enter/Exit Comparison, 1998 -- 2001; UA042.001.046.00011 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Compare, 1998 -- 2002; UA042.001.046.00012 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Previews, 1998 -- 2003; UA042.001.046.00013 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Student Survey, 1998; UA042.001.046.00014 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Student Survey, 1999; UA042.001.046.00015 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Student Survey, 2000; UA042.001.046.00016 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Student Survey, 2001; UA042.001.046.00017 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Student Survey, 2002; UA042.001.046.00018 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Student Survey, 2003; UA042.001.046.00019 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Entering Student Survey, Analysis of Three Classes, 1998 -- 2000; UA042.001.046.00020 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Exiting Student Survey, 1997; UA042.001.046.00021 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Exiting Student Survey, 1998; UA042.001.046.00022 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Exiting Student Survey, 1999; UA042.001.046.00023 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Exiting Student Survey Difference Between V94, V95, and V96, 1994 -- 1996; UA042.001.046.00024 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Exiting Students: Differences Between 94 and 95, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.046.00025 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Faculty Survey, 1999; UA042.001.046.00026 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM PEW Study, 1989; UA042.001.046.00027 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM Rotation Evaluation, 1996; UA042.001.046.00028 (Box 46)
  - TUSVM V96 Graduating Student Survey, 1996; UA042.001.046.00029 (Box 46)
  - University Positioning Study Revised, 2001; UA042.001.046.00030 (Box 46)
  - University Research Volume, 1998; UA042.001.046.00031 (Box 46)
  - U.S. News and World Report's Distance Education Survey Online Data Collection site, 2001; UA042.001.046.00032 (Box 46)
  - USAC Overview, 2002; UA042.001.046.00033 (Box 46)
  - USNRW - America's Best Medical Schools, 1995; UA042.001.046.00034 (Box 46)
  - USNRW - America's Best Medical Schools, 1998; UA042.001.046.00035 (Box 46)
  - Vet Alum, 1994; UA042.001.047.00001 (Box 47)
  - Vet Employers, 1980 -- 2000; UA042.001.047.00002 (Box 47)
  - Vet Faculty, 1980 -- 2000; UA042.001.047.00003 (Box 47)
  - Vet School, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.047.00004 (Box 47)
  - Vet School Comparative Report, 1985; UA042.001.047.00005 (Box 47)
  - Vet School Comparative Report, 1988; UA042.001.047.00006 (Box 47)
  - Vet School Faculty Comparative Report, 1994 -- 1999; UA042.001.047.00007 (Box 47)
  - Veterinary School Computer Use - Students, 1999; UA042.001.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - Win-Loss Accepted Applicants Matriculation Decisions, 1994; UA042.001.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - Academic Computing Survey - Computer Services, 1987; UA042.001.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - Admissions, 1997; UA042.001.047.00011 (Box 47)
  - Admissions Correlation, 1986; UA042.001.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - Age Distribution of Faculty Data for the Trustees, 1993; UA042.001.047.00013 (Box 47)
  - Alum Comments - Finals, 1994; UA042.001.047.00014 (Box 47)
  - Athletic Directors Salary, 1995; UA042.001.047.00015 (Box 47)
  - Budget Planning Survey, 1996; UA042.001.047.00016 (Box 47)
  - Budget Planning Survey, 1996 -- 1998; UA042.001.047.00017 (Box 47)
  - Budget Planning Survey, 1997; UA042.001.047.00018 (Box 47)
  - Budget Planning - Fall, 1998; UA042.001.047.00019 (Box 47)
  - Children Evaluation, 1999; UA042.001.047.00020 (Box 47)
  - Class of 1973 25th Reunion, 1998; UA042.001.047.00021 (Box 47)
  - Class Size, 1990; UA042.001.047.00022 (Box 47)
  - Clinical Assessment, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.047.00023 (Box 47)
  - COFHE - Fincancial Aid, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.047.00024 (Box 47)
  - Comparison Tuition and Fees, 1988; UA042.001.047.00025 (Box 47)
  - Comparative Enrollment by Race, 1995 -- 2000; UA042.001.047.00026 (Box 47)
  - Comparative Report - School of Dental Medicine, 1988; UA042.001.047.00027 (Box 47)
  - Comparative Stats, 1989; UA042.001.047.00028 (Box 47)
  - Comparative Student Charges, 1979 -- 1991; UA042.001.047.00029 (Box 47)
  - Comparative Student Charges, 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.047.00030 (Box 47)
  - Comparative Student Charges FY91-92 and FY89-90, 1989 -- 1993; UA042.001.047.00031 (Box 47)
  - Comparative Study of University Registrars, 1997; UA042.001.047.00032 (Box 47)
  - Computer Study - Computer Services, 1987; UA042.001.047.00033 (Box 47)
  - Consolidated Student Services Final Report, 1987; UA042.001.047.00034 (Box 47)
  - Convocation - London, 1996 -- 1998; UA042.001.047.00035 (Box 47)
  - Corporate Relations Request, 1990; UA042.001.047.00036 (Box 47)
  - Crime Statistics, 1994 -- 1998; UA042.001.047.00037 (Box 47)
  - Cumulative Financial Aid Packages, 1991 -- 1994; UA042.001.047.00038 (Box 47)
  - Data from Admissions Used for Minority Status Study, 1985; UA042.001.047.00039 (Box 47)
  - Employment Stats, 1987 -- 1990; UA042.001.047.00040 (Box 47)
  - Engineering Half Course, 1994; UA042.001.047.00041 (Box 47)
  - Enrollment, 1989; UA042.001.047.00042 (Box 47)
  - Enrollment by Race, 1996; UA042.001.047.00043 (Box 47)
  - Entering V98 and V99 Comparative Analysis, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.047.00044 (Box 47)
  - Exiting Comparisons V94 to V97, 1994 -- 1997; UA042.001.047.00045 (Box 47)
  - Exiting Student Survey - Differences V94 to V96, 1994 -- 1996; UA042.001.047.00046 (Box 47)
  - Faculty Comments, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.047.00047 (Box 47)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1994; UA042.001.047.00048 (Box 47)
  - Fin Aid, 1992 -- 1993; UA042.001.048.00001 (Box 48)
  - Fin Aid Across Tufts, 1988 -- 1989; UA042.001.048.00002 (Box 48)
  - Fin Aid Across Tufts Final Report, 1988 -- 1989; UA042.001.048.00003 (Box 48)
  - Fin Aid Class of 1994, 1990; UA042.001.048.00004 (Box 48)
  - Fin Aid Pack Study Class of 97, 1995; UA042.001.048.00005 (Box 48)
  - Fin Aid Package [1 of 2], 1995; UA042.001.048.00006 (Box 48)
  - Fin Aid Package [2 of 2], 1995; UA042.001.048.00007 (Box 48)
  - Fin Aid Packing Study 1995, 1996; UA042.001.048.00008 (Box 48)
  - 1994 Fin Aid Reply Form, UA042.001.048.00009 (Box 48)
  - Financial Aid, 1986 -- 1988; UA042.001.048.00010 (Box 48)
  - Financial Aid, 1988; UA042.001.048.00011 (Box 48)
  - Financial Aid Across Tufts, 1987 -- 1988; UA042.001.048.00012 (Box 48)
  - Financial Aid Across Tufts University, 1986 -- 1987; UA042.001.048.00013 (Box 48)
  - Financial Aid Across Tufts University, 1987 -- 1988; UA042.001.048.00014 (Box 48)